Out of 97 federal judges confirmed under Joe Biden, total number of white men, five.
22 are black women.
So this is race-based hiring.
It's illegal, but it's also not about looking like America.
It's about punishing people.
This man is dead serious and dangerous AF.
When you see the continual efforts and violence of clear people every day, you can blame media.
You can blame people like him and Fox News.
And the story that they're telling is that everybody else is being treated better than clear people.
Where?
And the people watching believe it.
Meanwhile, the reason why they don't have access to certain things, the reason why they don't have access to certain money is because the same people they're following are keeping them down.
It ain't us.
They do this because you can't have a ruling class unless you have a lower class that feels like as long as they're not the lowest class, it's okay to be ruled.
And the reason why they don't have access to certain things is because they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things, they don't have access to certain things.